Guide to the Gelman Library Assistant University Librarian for Collections records, 1951-1995 RG0108
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject files, 1967-2006; RG0108 Series 2; 0.5 Linear Feet
  - Collection Development Group, 1994-2006
    - Collection Development Group meetings [1 of 4], 2002-2006 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Collection Development Group meetings [2 of 4], 2002-2006 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Collection Development Group meetings [3 of 4], 2002-2006 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Collection Development Group meetings [4 of 4], 2002-2006 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Collection development policies, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Format guides, 2006, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Information [1 of 2], 1994-1999 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Information [1 of 2], 1994-1999 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - List, circa 1997 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Controversial material, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Collection Management Service
    - Collection management service, 1991-2002 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Collection Management Services, 2006 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Collection management service: backlog tracking /statistics, 1998-2006 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Damaged book review, 1989-2005 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - FRBR, circa 2005 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Backlog project, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Preservation and Binding Unit, 1996-2006 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Preservation and Binding Unit: background materials, 1985-1989 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Preservation and Binding Unit: binding contract, 1997-2004 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Consortium of Universities of the Washington Metropolitan Area, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Consortium of Universities of the Washington Metropolitan Area: Collection Development Task Force [1 of 2], 1980-1985 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Consortium of Universities of the Washington Metropolitan Area: Collection Development Task Force [2 of 2], 1980-1985 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Copyright [1 of 2], 1992-1999 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Copyright [2 of 2], 1992-1999 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Core competencies [1 of 2], 2002-2005 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Core competencies [2 of 2], 2002-2005 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Council of Librarians
    - Correspondence and memos, 1988-2004 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Grievance Committee, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Officers and committees, 1987-2006 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Professional Development Task Force, 1999-2001 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1986-1988 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1992-1994 August (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, 1994 September - 1995 September (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, 1994 December - 1999 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Minutes, 2000-2003 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 2004-2006 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Electronic journals, 1996-2001
      - Background materials, 1996-2001 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Collection development policies, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Ejournal packages, 2003-2006 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Ejournals working group, 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Licences - examples, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Licenses - provisions, etc., 1998-2002 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - LOCKSS, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - OVID and EBSCO, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - DSpace [1 of 2], 2005 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - DSpace [2 of 2], 2005 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - ebooks, 2000-2006
    - Background materials, 2000-2004 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Books 24x7, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Ebook Library, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Ebrary, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Google print libray project, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Safari e-books, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Other, 2000-2005 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Electronic resources, 1996-2006
    - Memos, reports, and minutes, 2001-2006 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Agendas, 1997-2001 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Cataloging [1 of 2], 1998-2004 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Cataloging [2 of 2], 1998-2004 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Collection development, 1996-2003 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Eresources list, 1999-2006 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - IP ranges, 1996-1999 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Security, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Selecting, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Title / aggregator evaluation, 1997-2002 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Use statistics, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Elicenses at General Counsel & Executive Vice President, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits, 1980-2006
    - Background materials, 1986-2000 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Budgets, 1996-2001 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Exhibits/events, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Exhibits/events, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Exhibits/events, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Exhibits/events, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Artists books, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Carnegie exhibit photographs, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
      Contains photographic proof sheet and 2 - 8x10 inch black and white photographs.
    - Goodbye Comrade, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Lost in the City, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Map exhibit, 1990 October (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - March on Washington [1 of 2], 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - March on Washington [2 of 2], 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Marcus Cunlifee: Scholar and Teacher, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Nabokov, Vladimir: exhibit and program, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - The peculiar advantage of place, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Political cartoonery in Washington, D.C., 1991 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Queerly visible, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Struggle without hate, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Student book collector's exhibit signs, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Travell, Janet. President's physician, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - 20 years of Special Collections at GW, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Unlimited book design, 1990 May (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Voteless city, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Older, 1980-1994 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Faculty authors, 1968-2004
      - Bibliography [1 of 2], 1968-1994 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Bibliography [2 of 2], 1968-1994 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Database, 1990-2001 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Exhibit, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Expenses, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Faculty, 1980-2004
    - General, 1988-1999 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Background/profiles, 1983-2001 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence/memos, 1994-2001 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Faculty handbook, 1986-1996 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Meetings, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Retirees/emeriti faculty, 1989-2003 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Twentyfive year honors, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - University professors, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Faculty and student user studies: final report, 1986 March 26 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Federal Depository Library Program, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Fee-based services, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Friends of the Library, 1996-2004
    - General, 1996-2004 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Meetings, 1996-1998 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Meetings, 1999-2002 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Newsletters, 1986-1999 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Student collections, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Fund codes, 1987-2002 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Funds, 1987-2006
    - GENX, GENF2, GENF3, 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - GENL orders, 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - GENL orders, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - GENL orders, 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - GENL orders, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - GENL orders, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - GENL orders, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - GENL orders, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - GENL orders, 2004-2005 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - GENL orders, 2005-2006 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - GENL - subscriptions [1 of 2], 2001-2006 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - GENL - subscriptions [2 of 2], 2001-2006 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - LAND orders, 2003-2005 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - LAND orders, 2005-2006 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - LAND subscriptions, 2003-2006 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - UNIVPROF, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - UNIVPROF orders, 1998-1999 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - UNIVPROF orders, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - UNIVPROF orders, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - UNIVPROF orders, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Univ Prof orders, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Univ Prof orders, 2004-2005 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Univ Prof orders, 2004-2005 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Univ Prof orders, 2005-2006 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Univ Prof orders, 2006-2007 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Univ Prof subscriptions, 1998-2005 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Gelman Library, 1967-2006 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Background material, 1967-2006 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Advancement Office, 1998-2000 (Box 31, Box 16)
    - Advancement Advisory Board, 2004-2006 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Advancement Group meetings, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Advancement Office funding ideas for donors, 1996-2006 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Guide, circa 1973 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Guides, 1983-1988 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Guides, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Guides, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Guides, 1999-2002 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Guides, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Guides, By George, 1993-1998 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Human Resources, 2000-2004 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Millenium Symposium, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Mission, 1994-2000 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Open houses / receptions, 1986-1993 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Organizational assessment, 1986-1991 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Organizational assessment, reorganization, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Organizational structure, 1993, undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Policies and procedures, 1988-1998 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Reorganization, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Review team, 1993 November (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Staff organization, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Student Advisory Board, 1997-2006
      - Meetings, 1998-2006 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Student Liaison orientation, 1997-2006 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Hatchet lunch meetings, 1997-2003 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Symposium series, 1996-2000 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - User surveys, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Website, 2001-2005 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Gelman Library System, 1999-2003
    - Employee guide [1 of 2], 1999 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Employee guide [2 of 2], 1999 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Guide for GW Faculty, 2001-2002 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Guide for GW Faculty, 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Official student guide, circa 2002 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - George Washington University, 1985-2006 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - General background materials, 1985-2004 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - 175th Anniversary, 1993-1995 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Academic Affairs Ten Years retrospective / submitted by Don Lehman, Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Colleges and Schools, 1988-2005
      - Background materials, 1997-2005 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - College of Professional Studies, 1997-2005 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Columbian College of Arts and Sciences, 1988-2003 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Elliott School of International Affairs, 1987-2004 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Graduate School of Education and Human Development, 1999-2002 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - School of Business and Public Management, 1990-1997 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - School of Engineering and Applied Science, 1990-2001 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Medical School, 1997-2000 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Departments
      - Art Department, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Center for Instructional Design and Development, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Chemistry, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Computational Science Program, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Early Modern European Studies, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Film Studies, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Globalization Institute, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Instructional Materials Center, 1991-1993 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Math, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Music, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - National Indian Policy Center, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Slavic Languages, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Sports and Sports Events Forum, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Offices, 1998-2001
      - Academic Development and Continuing Education, 1998-2001 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Center for Academic Technologies, 1999-2001 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - Development Office, 1989-2001 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Information Systems and Services, 1999-2004 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Information Systems and Services (ISS) plan, 2004 July (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - University Planning Office. Planning environments for the planning period, 1988-1993 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - University Planning Office. Data for the planning period, 1988-1993 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Faculty, 1991-1996
      - Faculty authors' publications, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Faculty authors' publications, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Faculty authors' publications, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Faculty authors' publications, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Faculty authors' publications, 1995-1996 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Financial report, 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - GW Research, circa 1998-2004 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Schedules to the financial statements for the year ended June 30, 2002. Vol. 1, 2001-2002 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Schedules to the financial statements for the year ended June 30, 2002. Vol. 2, 2001-2002 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Senior staff retreat, 2002 December 23 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Student Association, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Campus, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Gift books received since Penny arrived, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Government documents, 1978-2006
    - Census depository, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Draft letter to Mayor Marion Barry, 1982 November 8 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - 1983 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - 1984 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - 1987 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - 1991 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - 1992 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - 1993 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - 1994 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - 1996 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - 1997 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - 1999 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - 2000 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - 2001 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - 2002 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - 2004 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - 2005 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - 2006 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Inspection report results, 1997-2003 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Gelman selections, 1983-1991 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Depository selection, 1989 June - 1997 June (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Depository selection, 1988-2002 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - GPO tapes from MARCIVE, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Integration into LC Stacks, 1993-1998 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Future of government documents in ARL libraries [1 of 2], 1993-2005 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Future of government documents in ARL libraries [2 of 2], 1993-2005 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - GWorld, 1996-2002 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Himmelfarb Library, 1990-2004
    - 1997-2004 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - HKLS (exercise science), 1990-1996 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - HSMP, 1996-1998 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Honors program, 1991-2004
    - 2004 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - University Symposium pathfinders and reading packets, 1991-2001 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - User education, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Readings, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Readings, 1996 March (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Readings, 1996 October (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Readings, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Readings, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Insurance, 1993-2004
    - 1993 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - 1994 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - 1996 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - 1997 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - 1998 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - 1999 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - 2000 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - 2001 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - 2002 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - 2003 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - 2004 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - 2005 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Interlibrary loan, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Inventory, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Inventory, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Japan Foundation, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - LibQual survey [1 of 2], 2003 Spring - 2004 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - LibQual survey [2 of 2], 2003 Spring - 2004 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Librarian reorganization, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Library Impact Statements, 1992-2005
    - 1992-1999 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - 2000-2002 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - 2003-2005 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Council of Deans presentation, 1999 November (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Database, 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Memos, 1990-2004 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Other reports, 1998-2005 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - University Librarian's reports, 1998-2000 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Library Seminar: Earlham College - Library & classroom strategies for matching resources with courses, 1985 November 22 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Lisner, 1977-1990 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Local area network, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Location codes, 1997-2006 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Lost/missing, 1988-1996 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Lost/missing: replacements, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - LS/2, 1988-2002
    - Correspondence/memos, 1988-2002 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Equipment, 1988-2002 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Hardware, 1989-1990 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Maintenance, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Problems, 1989-1990 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Upgrades, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Machine readable data files, 1989-1997 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - MARC, 1988-1992 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - MARCIVE, 1986-1993
    - Background materials, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Contract, 1988-1993 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence/memos, 1988-1993 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Equipment, 1988-1990 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - GPO, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Maintenance, 1988-1990 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Master calendar, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Media Department [1 of 2], 1985-1999 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Media Department [2 of 2], 1985-1999 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Media collections statistics, 1993-1995 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Microforms, 1983-1985 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Microforms: contract negotiation, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Microform Conversion Project, 1985-1986
    - Background materials, circa 1985 - circa 1986 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence/memos, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Periodical retainer titles, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - UMI agreements, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - UMI price quotations, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Mt. Vernon campus, 1997-2006
    - Background material, 1997-2006 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 2001-2006 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Cataloging, 1998-2002 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - NACUBO benchmarks, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) funds for collections, 1988-1996 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - National Security Archive, 1991-2004 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - NTIS, 1988-1998 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Non-print materials [1 of 2], 1989-1995 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Non-print materials [2 of 2], 1988-1998 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Non-print Materials Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - North American Title Count, 1989-2001 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Northeast Research Libraries (NERL) [1 of 2], 2001-2005 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Northeast Research Libraries (NERL) [2 of 2], 2001-2005 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - OCLC, 1997-2003 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - OCLC cataloging, 1994-1999 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Pcard use study, 2004-2005 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Performance appraisal, 1987-2005
    - Performance appraisal [1 of 2], 1987-2001 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Performance appraisal [2 of 2], 1987-2001 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Performance appraisal criteria, 1993-200 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Performance appraisal procedures, 1988-1994 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Performance appraisal procedures, 1997-1999 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Performance appraisal process, electronic files, etc., 1997-1998 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Performance appraisal workshop, 1992 May (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Performance appraisal workshop, 1993 June (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Performance appraisal classified staff, 1993-2001 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Periodicals cancellations, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Periodicals use study, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Personnel, background materials, 1993-2001 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Photocopy center, 1983-1988 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Policy & Procedures -- Renaissance Times, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Preservation, 1999-2005 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Preservation background materials, 1987-1990 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Program reviews, 1988-1996
    - Program reviews 1, 1989-1996 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Program reviews 1 general, 1988-1993 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Program reviews 1 schedules, 1989-1994 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Program reviews 2 subspec retreat, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Program reviews 2 recommendations [1 of 2], 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Program reviews 2 recommendations [2 of 2], 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Program reviews, 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Programs/Services: Telecommunications Information Center [1 of 2], 1982-1985 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Programs/Services: Telecommunications Information Center [2 of 2], 1982-1985 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Reference weed, 2005-2006 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Research Libraries Group, 1980-1989 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Background information, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - North American College Inventory project, circa 1984 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Research Libraries Information Network (RLIN) [1 of 2], 1980-1989 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Research Libraries Information Network (RLIN) [2 of 2], 1980-1989 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Scholarly Communication, 1999-2004
    - General, 2001-2004 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Power Point, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Webpage, 1999-2004 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Scholars Express [1 of 2], 1999-2000 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Scholars Express [2 of 2], 1999-2000 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Senate (GW) Committee on Fiscal Planning and Budget, 1999-2002 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Senate (GW) Committee on Libraries, 1999-2006
    - 1999-2002 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - 2005-2006 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - 2005-2006 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Serials, 1987-1994
    - Cleanup, 1992-1994 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - List, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Final - to store, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Final - not to store, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Final - classed and not considered, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Memos, action plans, manp of Lisner, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Journal citation reports, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Reviews, 1988-2005
      - General information, 1990-1994 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Serials use studies, 1991-1995 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - 1988 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - 1988 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Serials cancellations over $500 list, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - [1 of 3], 1999-2000 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - [2 of 3], 1999-2000 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - [3 of 3], 1999-2000 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - 2005 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Shelf-ready books, 1999-2002
    - Shelf-ready books, 1999-2002 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Shelf-ready books [1 of 2], 1996-2004 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Shelf-ready books [2 of 2], 1996-2004 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Shelf-ready books tape loading, 1999-2000 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Shelving contract, 1991-2007
    - Contracts, 1991-1994 (Box 52, Folder 1)